[
    {
        "question": "Whats my favourite name??",
        "choice1": "Thabo",
        "choice2": "Keorapetse",
        "choice3": "Molefi",
        "choice4": "None of the above",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would I rather be now?",
        "choice1": "In my home with my wife",
        "choice2": "Next to my mum",
        "choice3": "In the MDiHub",
        "choice4": "Compton",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How much do I miss alcohol?",
        "choice1": "A lot, like I would kill for a glass of Amstel",
        "choice2": "Not much...",
        "choice3": "Nothing at all",
        "choice4": "I accasionally miss it",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What's my favorite clothing brand?",
        "choice1": "Rossimoda",
        "choice2": "DMD Dwep Mo' Dwep",
        "choice3": "Carvela",
        "choice4": "Dickies",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Whos my favorite house artist?",
        "choice1": "Ooh Shucks",
        "choice2": "Da Capo",
        "choice3": "Black Motion",
        "choice4": "Kususa",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's my favourite rapper of all time?",
        "choice1": "Tupac",
        "choice2": "Kendrick Lamar",
        "choice3": "Nipsey Hussle",
        "choice4": "YoungstaCPT",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What's my life motto?",
        "choice1": "Love",
        "choice2": "Feminism",
        "choice3": "Spirituality",
        "choice4": "Respect",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What saved me?",
        "choice1": "The Bible",
        "choice2": "Tupac Shakur and hip hop",
        "choice3": "Sir Max",
        "choice4": "My family",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do I draw motivation from in my life?",
        "choice1": "Life",
        "choice2": "Where I come from",
        "choice3": "Where I wanna go",
        "choice4": "Keaoleboga",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my purpose in life?",
        "choice1": "Enlightenment",
        "choice2": "To program",
        "choice3": "To write",
        "choice4": "Yet to be descovered",
        "answer": 1
    }
]